SNEHAL BHAGWATE

Software Engineer

CONTACT

- +91-7218336380
- ✓ snehalporatkar10g@gmail.com
- B-1601, R16 Sector Society, Life Republic Township, Marunji, Hinjewadi, Pune 411057

EDUCATION

2008 - 2011 NAGPUR UNIVERSITY

- Bachelor of Engineering (I.T.)
- Per. 69.22 %

2005 - 2008 NAGPUR UNIVERSITY

- Diploma (Information Technology)
- Per. 75.83 %

2004 - 2005 MAHARSHTRA STATE BOARD

- 10 th
- Per. 75.20 %

LANGUAGES

- English
- Hindi
- Marathi

SKILLS

- Project Management
- Teamwork
- Time Management
- Leadership
- Effective Communication
- Critical Thinking

PROFILE SUMMARY

As a motivated Full Stack Developer, I bring SDLC and Agile experience, delivering high-quality web applications with precision and accuracy. I excel in problem-solving, with a strong background in internships, freelancing, and developing "Devaten", a database performance tool.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Growsoft Technologies LLP

01/2024 - PRESENT

Full-Stack Inter

- Developing and maintaining front-end and back-end components of web applications.
- Ensuring high-quality code delivery and meeting project deadlines.
- Staying up-to-date with industry trends and emerging technologies.
- Utilizing tools and technologies such as front-end and back-end frameworks, databases, version control systems, and agile project management tool.

Freelancer

09/2023 - 01/2024

Freelancer

- Building responsive, user-friendly, and scalable websites.
- Writing clean, efficient, and well-documented code.
- Collaborating with clients to understand project requirements and deliver tailored solutions.
- Staying up-to-date with industry trends and emerging technology.

TrioNxt Software Solutions Pvt .Ltd

04/2022 - 06/2023

Junior Software Engineer

- Developing and testing software applications with precision and accuracy.
- Collaborating with teams to identify and prioritize project requirements.
- Writing clean, efficient, and well-documented code.
- Troubleshooting and debugging code issues with ease.

Tata Capital

10/2016 - 02/2019

Executive

- Developing and implementing strategic plans to enhance customer experience and improve operational efficiency.
- Managing and motivating teams to achieve sales, service, and quality targets.
- Analyzing performance metrics and implementing data-driven solutions to optimize results.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Java(Spring Boot, REST Api, java 8, Hibernate)
- HTML
- CSS
- Bootstrap
- JavaScript
- Angular7
- Angular Js
- Microservices
- React Native
- React Express
- Node JS
- Data Analysis
- MySQL
- STS (Spring Boot Soot)
- Eclipse
- VS code
- Postman
- Swagger
- Windows
- MS- Office
- Tomcat
- Xampp
- Jira
- Slack
- Confluence
- Bit-bucket
- Git-Hub
- Software Development Life Cycle

PERSONAL VITAL

• **DOB**: 13/01/1990

 Strength: Friendly Nature, Good Communication Skill.

• Hobbies: Gardening, Baking cakes

Ni-Lux Software

Web Developer

05/2014 - 12/2014

- Design and develop responsive, user-friendly, and scalable websites.
- Write clean, efficient, and well-documented code.
- Collaborate with clients to understand project requirements and deliver tailored solutions.

Umrer Polytechnic Collage

Lecturer

05/2014 - 12/2014

- Teach and mentor students in various subjects, promoting academic excellence and personal growth.
- Develop and deliver engaging lesson plans, ensuring curriculum requirements are met.
- Assess student performance, providing constructive feedback and guidance.

PROJECTS

- CSE-PRO (Feb 2024 Jun 2024, Malaysia)
 - Technologies: REACT, HTML, CSS, BOOTSTRAP, MYSQL, GIT
 - Description: Monitored and controlled warehouse operations and materials.
- My Portfolio (Jan 2024 Feb 2024, India)
 - Technologies: HTML, CSS, Git Hub (https://github.com/snehalporatkar/)
 - Description: Developed a personal portfolio website to showcase skills and experience.
- Snehdeep (Sep 2023 Dec 2023, India)
 - o Technologies: HTML, CSS, Git Hub
 - Git-Hub URL: https://app.devaten.com/
 - Description: Developed a website for a physiotherapist's services and appointments.
- Devaten (Jul 2022 Jun 2023, Netherlands)
 - Technologies: Angular, JAVA, HTML, MYSQL, JIRA, Bitbucket
 - URL: https://app.devaten.com/
 - Description: Developed a database performance monitoring app.
- Teen Talks Android Mobile App and Web App (April 2022 Jul 2022, India)
 - Technologies: Angular, JAVA, Ionic, MYSQL, JIRA, Bitbucket
 - Description: Developed an app for adolescent health and care education.